http://www.millertanner.com/privacy-and-usage/

Face-to-Face (in
person)
Exceptional in-person experience for all your attendees.
Screen-to-Screen (virtual)
Meeting even when attendees can’t gather.
Hybrid (combination)
The best of both worlds and the future of events.
ATTEND™ Paperless Events
Increase engagement with your attendees throughout an event. Featuring event notifications,
expense reimbursements, travel confirmations, agendas and more.
EPIC™ Event Planning in Control
Gain instant access to your event details with our event management app. Includes real-time
deviations, attendee registration metrics
and more.
VALTs™ Virtual Assessment Learning and Training Source
Deliver training content, capture the live event for those unable to attend and create assessments
to validate comprehension.
About MTA
Our Team
At MTA, it really is all about the people.
Testimonials
Don't take it from us. See what our clients have to say.
Our Privacy Policy
At Miller Tanner, we understand how important it is to our customers that the information we collect from you remains confidential and private. We take our responsibility to protect your information seriously and have implemented policies and security safeguards to help ensure your data is properly protected. Please see our full Privacy Policy HERE.
Cookies and How We Use Them
A cookie is a small data file stored on your computer or mobile device at the request of your browser from a website when you visit this website. Cookies allow the website to ‘remember’ your actions or preferences. Learn more about how Miller Tanner Associates uses cookies HERE.
Subject Request Form
You have a choice related to your personal information, and a simple way to inform us of your decision. If you wish to access your personal information maintained at Miller Tanner Associates, please fill out the form located HERE.
© 2020 Miller Tanner Associates. All rights reserved.
Privacy Policy & Use of Personal Information
Go
